zuslist.com 2012-06-24

# Privacy Policy - Classifieds | Classifieds Ads

| 

**Privacy Policy**

[ZUSlist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this. [ZUSlist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) uses the information collected to provide you with personalized services, and to facilitate activities such as managing and editing your ads, messages, and account information. 

Information about your computer hardware and software is automatically collected by global-[ZUSlist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) and may be shared with third parties whose services are used for traffic analysis purposes. This information includes: your browser type, IP address, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by [ZUSlist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) to maintain and improve the quality of the service and to generate statistics regarding use of the [ZUSlist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) site.

Financial information, such as credit card numbers and bank account information, is not collected on our site.

[ZUSlist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) collects information from users responding to ads regarding their Internet provider; this information may include the user's IP address, host name, country of origin and Internet provider being used. This collected information may be shared with the user placing the ad for the sole purpose of assisting this user in determining the validity and legitimacy of the response. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We may use information collected to promote other affiliate programs, products, [web sites](http://global-free-classified-ads.com/dir/index.html) and services. 

**Personal Descriptions and Upload of Photos**  
In an effort to facilitate a trusting buying and selling community, we provide you with the option to submit pictures and/or a description of your item or service. When you post your classified ad on [ZUSlist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/), the ad description and pictures are displayed on the site and accessible to visitors on [ZUSlist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/). Classifieds and photos are subject to approval and must meet the [_Disclaimer and Terms of Use_](http://www.zuslist.com/Disclaimer-and-Terms-of-Use/).

**Cookies**   
[ZUSlist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) uses cookies to provide you access to protected pages without requesting a login each time. Cookies are small files that are placed on your computer when you visit our site. Our web site will reference and update the cookie each time you visit [ZUSlist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/). We use cookies to deliver content specific to you, for pages such as Your stuff. We accomplish this by storing encrypted information that uniquely identifies you in a cookie. 

**Public Access to Information**   
Exercise caution the information that you post at [ZUSlist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/), or when rate other members, and/or respond to ratings of other members, is posted in public areas and available to all visitors. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. 

**Security**   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. All member data and activity is stored separately and is not directly accessible through a web browser. We use industry standard procedures and processes to safeguard the confidentiality of your identifiable personal information, such as firewalls, encryption, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. Unfortunately, when you submit information about yourself to [Zuslist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) over the Internet, the information may travel over many systems that are not under the control of [Zuslist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/). The Internet is not 100% secure and others might intercept the information that you are sending. Remember that your account is accessible only through the use of your Password. 

**Access to Your Personal Information**  
Our priority is to keep your personal information private and confidential. [Zuslist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) will not willfully disclose, rent, or sell your personal information to third parties. However, certain personal information will be available to others in the process of using [Zuslist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/). For example, visitors to [Zuslist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) may view your member name, feedback rating, city, and items you have for sale. 

Of course, once you provide personal information to a buyer or seller, [Zuslist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) has no control over how that information might be used by that individual. In addition, should you circumvent our on-site messaging system, [Zuslist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) will be unable to provide assistance in transaction disputes. We recommend using our messaging system for any communications between you and potential buyers and sellers. 

[ZUSlist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) may choose to disclose your personally identifiable information to others Only If you consent to share your information, and/or your actions on [Zuslist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) appear to be in violation of our policies (including, but not limited to, our [_Disclaimer and Terms of Use_](http://www.zuslist.com/Disclaimer-and-Terms-of-Use/) , and Fees and Payments policies) and/or you post a classified ad which we believe, in our sole discretion, may create a liability for [Zuslist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/), and/or in the case of a criminal investigation, subpoena, court order or legal process. 

Nothing in this policy shall limit, prohibit, or otherwise deny the ability of [Zuslist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) to (1) transfer, assign, or sell our assets to a third party without limitation, or (2) dispose of our assets in any manner, through bankruptcy or similar proceeding. In addition, [Zuslist.com](http://www.zuslist.com/) makes no warranties or claims regarding the accuracy or completeness of the information we collect and disclose through our site, and disclaims any liability regarding its use.
